JAYESH

DANKHARA

Android Application Developer (Freelancer)

Contact

Address:

Surat, Gujarat

Phone:

+91 93280 10435

Email:

jayesh17296@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

<u>linkedin.com/ in/dankhara-jayesh-429965179</u>

Portfolio:

https://jayeshdankhara.github.io/

Languages

English Gujarati Hindi

Hobbies

- Writing
- Music
- Photography
- Traveling
- Design

Summary

Assist in software architecture development, prototyping, debugging and testing Reviewing Product Feature Specifications and creating design documentation and Test Plans. Scripting and coding of test cases Lab support including server installation, backup and replacement Hands on coding in C, C++, Java, Kotlin, SQL, SQLiteProvidecradle-to-grave oversight of software project management, leading the research, design, development, documentation, testing and rollout of enterprise applications

Skill

- C,C++, JAVA,Kotlin
- REST APIs
- JSON,GSON
- HTML,CSS
- Networking
- Working with data
- Firebase Services
- Geolocation Services

- Android SDK
- MSQL,SQLite
- Push Notifications
- Complex problem solver
- Social Networks Integration

Experience

Moblie Application Development

Creative Design & Multimedia Institute Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

Iroid Solution Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

Poppins IT solution Sep 2020 - Mar 2021

hare krishna exports pvt ltd Apr 2021 - Jan 2022

Education

V.N.S.G.U. (2015 to 2018)

Bachelor of Computer Application

CGPA: 7.57

Shri Shambhubhai V. Patel College of Computer Science

Higher Secondary Education (2013)

12 Aggregate score: 68.13%

Prerna Vidhayalay

Secondary Education (2011)

10 aggregate score: 68.00%

Shree Bhavganga High School